An Inventory of the United States. Food Administration records XX066
Hoover Institution Archives
- Oversize materials, 1911-1932 (Folder 446-478)
  - Office Director Edgar Rickard, Food Administration building, Washington D. C., floor plans, circa 1917 (Folder 475: 3)
  - Fats and Oils Division, 1917-1918 (Folder 475: 4)
  - Edwin Paul Shattuck files, United States Grain Corporation, daily price, 1919 (Folder 475: 5)
  - Grain, Acreage Sown and Abandoned Average 1914-1917 (Folder 475: 6)
  - Bread and baking, 1917-1919 (Folder 475: 7)
  - Food conservation clippings, 1917-1919 (Folder 475: 8)
  - War Trade Board, 1917-1918 (Folder 476)
    - "Average Weekly Ration for Different Localities in Germany,", 1918 (Folder 476: 1)
    - "Daily Report of Licenses Granted by All Offices on Food,", 1917-1918 (Folder 476: 2-6)
    - "Weekly Report of Licenses Granted by All Offices on Food,", 1917 (Folder 476: 7)
    - "Special Report of Licenses on Food,", 1917 (Folder 476: 8)
    - "Exports of Food and Feedstuffs, Including Live Animals from United States,", 1918 (Folder 476: 9-10)
    - "Summary of Actual Reports,", 1918 (Folder 477: 1)
    - "Licenses Granted by All Offices for Export to Mexico,", 1918 (Folder 477: 2)
    - "Licenses Granted by All Offices for Export of Food,", 1917-1918 (Folder 477: 3-8)
  - Grain, 1916-1918
    - Movements of corn, rye, and oats, 1918 (Folder 478: 1)
    - "Wheat Supply and Distribution,", 1918 (Folder 478: 1)
    - Corn and corn products, 1918 (Folder 478: 2)
    - Rice millers-domestic, 1918 (Folder 478 :3)
  - Canned goods, 1917-1919 (Folder 478: 4)
  - Cold Storage Warehousemen reports, 1918-1919 (Folder 478: 5-6)
  - Exports and imports, 1911-1919 (Folder 478)
    - "Summary of Exports from the United States for the Fiscal Years 1917-18 and 1918-1919" (Folder 478: 7)
    - "Export of Food Stuffs from the United States,", 1911-1918 (Folder 478)
    - "World Situation on Meats and Animal Fats,", 1909-1919 (Folder 478: 8)
    - Imports into the United Kingdom by Countries for Pre-War Years, 1911-1914 (Folder 478: 9)
    - Imports to the United States, 1912-1918 (Folder 478: 10-11)
  - Sugar, 1918 (Folder 478)
    - "Sources of the British, French and Italian Sugar Supply before and during the War,", 1918 (Folder 478: 12)
    - "Exports of Sugar from Cuba to Europe,", 1918 (Folder 478)
  - Wheat and flour, Comparative Chart of Total Receipts of Flour and Wheat, 1916-1917. (Folder 478: 13)
    See also Alphabetical file, Grain, Wheat and Flour